<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="all">All</string>
  <string name="social">Social</string>
  <string name="data">Data</string>
  <string name="tech">Tech</string>
  
  <string name="descriptionLabel">Description</string>
  <string name="timePlaceLabel">Time and Place</string>
  <string name="speakersLabel">Participating</string>
  <string name="biographyLabel">Biography</string>
  <string name="tweetsLabel">Twitter Feed</string>

	<string name="working">GATHERING DATA FROM THE CLOUD...</string>
	<string name="email">E-Mail</string>
	<string name="password">Password</string>
	<string name="authenticating">Authenticating...</string>
	<string name="leave">Leave the application?</string>
	<string name="ok">OK</string>
	<string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
	<string name="appcNetwork">LOG IN BELOW WITH YOUR APPCELERATOR.COM CREDENTIALS</string>
	<string name="noAppcNetwork">Need an account? Get one here ></string>
	<string name="login">Log In</string>
	<string name="logout">Log Out</string>
	<string name="loginError">Login Error</string>
	<string name="loginErrorText">Oops! There was a problem logging in to your developer account. Please check your e-mail and password and try again.</string>
	<string name="logoutError">Sign Out Error</string>
	<string name="logoutErrorText">We were unable to reach our servers to end your session.  Please check your network connection and try again.</string>
	<string name="uhwhat">I don't have any of those...</string>
	<string name="alreadyDid">I already signed up with a new account.</string>
	<string name="thatscool">No account? That's cool, sign up here instead...</string>
	<string name="ohnice">Already have an account? Sweet, log in here.</string>
	<string name="signup">Sign Up</string>
	<string name="forgot">Forgot your password?</string>
	<string name="networkErrTitle">Network Access Required</string>
	<string name="networkErrMsg">It looks like your device is not connected to the internet. Please check your network settings and try again.</string>
	<string name="networkGenericErrorTitle">Network Error</string>

	<string name="venueCaps">VENUE</string>
	<string name="thirdFloor">3RD FLOOR</string>
	<string name="fourthFloor">4TH FLOOR</string>

	<string name="agendaCaps">AGENDA</string>
	<string name="day1">Day 1</string>
	<string name="day2">Day 2</string>
	<string name="sessionData">Fetching session data...</string>
	<string name="agendaNetworkError">We were unable to retrieve session data at this time.  Please check your network connection and then press the refresh button to try again.</string>
	<string name="tweetsNetworkError">We were unable to retrieve twitter data at this time.  Please check your network connection and then press the refresh button to try again.</string>
	
	<string name="aboutHeader">THIS APP WAS CREATED BY :</string>
	<string name="development">Centogram specializes in content-managed mobile apps where we pride ourselves in delivering thoughtful strategy and design to all screens - atop desks and in hands.  We deliver solutions to Fortune 500 companies across the nation, and we work hard to exceed their very high expectations of us.</string>
  <string name="design">Mike Zitt Inc creates brand experiences that grow businesses. We are focused on making complex messages simple, with a passion and proven understanding of the mobile landscape. We can start from the beginning of a project or anywhere in the development cycle to deliver with excellence.</string>
  <string name="technologyApp">This application was built with Appcelerator, the number one platform for cloud service-enabled mobile applications. Application logic was developed using Alloy, a component-oriented client side MVC framework for Titanium that provides declarative markup for native UI, separation of concerns, and a predictable project structure for Titanium applications.</string>
  <string name="technologyBack">The back end for this app is implemented using Drupal which enables a feature-rich back end to manage the content.</string>

  <string name="sourceLabel">OPEN SOURCE</string>
  <string name="source">This application is open source under the Apache 2.0 License, and is available for download at http://bit.ly/dnc-src</string>
  
  
  <string name="favoritesHelp">You can create your personal Schedule by clicking on the star icon in the Schedule Tab next to each session you wish to attend. The star will turn blue and a link to the Session will be created here for your personal schedule. That's it!. 
    </string>
  
  
  
</resources>